Guide to the Norma Bicknell and Robert Stuart Mansfield Papers 1929-1970
Special Collections and University Archives, University of Oregon Libraries
- Manuscripts (Robert Mansfield)
  - The Pemmican Skin (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Tragedy (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Two Dollars For a Marriage License (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Very Sincerely (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - You Gotta Be Tough (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - You'll Never Lose (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Publications (Robert Mansfield)
  - "Acquittal" Etc., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Air Nerve" The Haversack, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Arsenals In the Desert" The Haversack (Ch. 1-10), 1930-1931 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Back of Five Fingers" The Haversack (Ch. 1-10), 1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Bad One" Liberty, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Bequest" Colliers, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Black Arrows" The Haversack, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Black Light" The Torchbearer, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Bullet Bait" Detective Tales, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Cache of the Atoll" The Haversack (Ch. 1-8), 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "The City Towards the Sun" The Haversack (Ch. 1-11), 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Close Formation" The Haversack, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "College Money" The Haversack, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Copy Boy" The Classmate, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Don't Call It a Game" The Haversack, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "The Dragon Jar" The High Road, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Eyes of Congo" The Haversack (Ch. 1-4), 1927 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Fishin'" The Haversack, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Going Home" Liberty, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Gunwales Awash" The Haversack (Ch. 1-2), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Handy Man" The Classmate, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Handy Man" The High Road, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Handy Man" The Wellspring, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "I've Been Writing for boys" The Quill, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Lacquer Box" The Epworth Highroad, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "The Lure of the Rod and Chain" The High Road, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "A Matter of Honor" The Torchbearer, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Mott Street Irregulars" The Epworth Highroad, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "No More Romance" Family Circle, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Once Around the Mountain" Saturday Evening Post, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Once Around the Mountain" Storyteller, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "One Dog Died" The Epworth Highroad, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Pei Kuan Scroll" The Pilgrim Highroad, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "The Perplexing Adventure of Mr. Brint" Liberty, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Salesmanship" The Classmate, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Salesmanship" The Wellspring, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Sea Lion Cave" The Haversack (Part I-III), 1928 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "The Semaphore" Colliers, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Semov's Island" The Torchbearer, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Semov's Strategy" The Torchbearer, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Shutter Bugs" Liberty, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Sluice-Box Ranch" The Haversack (Ch. 1-4), 1936 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Special Delivery" The Torchbearer, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Such Outworn Notions" The Family Circle, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Sutter's Crystal" Liberty, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Take It Easy" The Haversack, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Ten Men and An Echo" Liberty, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Travel Light" The Haversack, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Treasure of Fond au Blanc" The Haversack (Ch. 1-6), 1927 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "A Use for Money" The Epworth Highroad, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "A Use for Money" The Pilgrim Highroad, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "What's new at Ann Arbor" DAC News, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Just Be Yourself" J. B. Lippincott and Co., 1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Team Play" Farmer Rinehart, Inc., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Towboats to the Orient" Mansfield and William L. Worden, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)